Guide to the Marine Workers Historical Collection TAM 125
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- Series I: General Files, 1930-1996
  - Reed, Clarence: Oral History Transcript, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Research Resources in Maritime Labor History, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Robinson, Edward (Frenchy): Testimonial Dinner, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Rubin, Harry: "In the Case of Morrissey and Ibrahim v. Curran et al.," (pamphlet), 1980 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Sanjines, Carl: Correspondence with Marine Workers Historical Association, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Seamen’s International Union (SIU) Strike: "Draft of Compromise Suggested to Committee of Ship Owners", 1936 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - SIU Strike: Marine Cooks’ and Stewards’ Union, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Seamen’s Defense Committee against Coast Guard Screening, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Scuttlebutt from the Waterfront(Vol. II, no. 1), Randall B. Smith, editor, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Ship Channel Progressive Committee: "Ship Channel," Newsletter (photocopies), 1936-1937 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Smith, Edwin Seymour: Obituaries, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Smith, Fredrick CA.: Proceedings of Testimonial Dinner in Honor of, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Sordes, George H.: NMU Card and Picket Cards, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Spanish Civil War: "How Franco Works, Part I," Clipping, NMU Pilot, Apr 1943 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Stack, Joseph: Trial Proceedings, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Stack, Joseph: "I Used to Cry When I Heard the Star Spangled Banner," Autobiography (typescript), undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Szeliga (Michel), Loretta: Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Szeliga, Loretta: Memorabilia from Women’s Auxiliary of the NMU, 1939-1946 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Taft, Philip: "Civil Rights in the National Maritime Union," Report (typescript), 1950 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Tank, Herbert: Communists on the Waterfront(pamphlet), 1946 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Tank, Herbert: Longitude 49, Book Cover and Photos, Posters, and Reviews of Play, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Tank, Herbert: NMU Identification and Financial Papers, 1942-1951 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - U.S. Merchant Marine Veterans (WWII): The Gangway(Vol. 2, No., 5-6; photocopies), 1985-1985 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Weiner, Morris: Account of Anti-Semitic Incident aboard the SS Pan Maryland, undated (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Weiner, Morris: Charges against Traveler’s Insurance, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Weiner, Morris: Complaint of Misconduct against Seymour Besunder, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Weiner, Morris: NMU Expulsion, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Weiner, Morris: Membership in TWU Local 504, 1985-1991 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Weiner, Morris: Personal Papers, 1936-1986 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Weiner, Morris: Research on David Shapiro, 1949-1989 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Weiner, Morris: Signal Corps Radio Operators Manual and Q Signal Chart, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Women’s Auxiliary of the NMU: First Anniversary Ball, Program, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 54)